♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix this ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
He's searching for something.
But he doesn't know how.
[Kurt] I saw the thief on the CCTV!
How can you be sure?
[Kurt] The diamond tattoos on his fingers!
In fairness, you're sharp.
If he already has five million,
why is he still vulcanizing tires
at that shop?
[Atoy] Pretend to be customers,
or whatever you want.
What matters is you get inside.
Patch!
Mmm. [smirks]
- Yes. [in English] Hello, boss!
- [Emerson, in Italian] Yes.
[Boyet] Yes. Your suitcase is here.
The money is safe. Don't worry.
So, boss? Do you want me to count it?
[Emerson, in English] Athena Hotel,
Olive Function Room.
That's where he'll meet his Boss KM.
We need to get the money
from Boyet before he gives it to KM!
[in English] This man
is a master of disguise.
[in English] Do you know this man?
‪PREVIOUSLY
[Audrey, in English] No.
[Atoy] Someone must pose
as a buyer at the auction.
Don't involve Karla.
[Emerson] I'll handle it.
We'll fix this. I'll update you.
Bring me along, please.
I don't want to be left behind,
just worrying about you.
Atoy will scold me. He'll be mad.
He doesn't need to know, right?
Come on, I'll help.
[clicks tongue]
[music concludes]
Come on!
Fine! Yes! Yes! Okay, okay!
Go inside now.
I'll just get something from the shop.
When I get back,
we'll come up with a plan.
Thank you, brother! Thanks!
- [Emerson] You're so persistent.
- You're so handsome! Idol!
Karla.
- Oh?
- I'll join your mission.
[in English] Maybe you need
one more hand.
Psst. Keep quiet.
They don't know you know
Brother Atoy's side job.
And Brother Emerson won't allow it.
You're Red Regalia's son.
So, let's keep it a secret then.
Oh, so it's like
a secret mission with you,
without Brother Atoy knowing.
You're such a gossip.
I just overheard. Come on, Karla.
I'll help you.
I'll make sure you're safe.
Come on.
Why don't you just help Cathy?
Maybe she's busy in the barangay.
- Go check.
- No.
I'd rather be with you.
[pleasant music playing]
- What?
- No.
I mean, it's more exciting
to join the mission.
- Ah. The mission.
- Right? Come on, Karla. Please.
Fine.
Yes!
- [in English] Game.
- Psst.
Just don't tell anyone.
I'll let you know the plan.
- [in English] Okay.
- And…
Brother Emerson
must never know you're joining.
[in English] Okay. Copy, boss.
- [in English] Okay?
- [in English] Okay.
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[music intensifies]
- [clicking]
- [snipping]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[in English] This is composite.
It's 99% accurate.
[in English] Why are you doubting it now?
[in English] This is the woman
we met in the embassy.
[in English] She's very beautiful,
that is why I doubt.
[in English] You mentioned
that it's AI-generated, right?
- [in English] Yes.
- [in English] So, doesn't that mean that
there's a chance that maybe
the composition is wrong?
[man, in English]
Is she even interested in you?
[in English] Well, she gave me her number.
[in English] So, yes.
[in English] Why don't you just call her
and stop questioning my skills?
[pensive music playing]
[in English] I will.
[line ringing]
Hello?
[in English] Hello, Ms. Audrey.
This is Samir.
[in English] I know
that we, uh, just spoke,
but I'd like to know
if you'd want to go on a date?
Oh!
[in English] Really?!
[in English] See. She likes me.
[playful music playing]
[in English] Ah, when are you available?
[in English] Anytime!
[in English] Anytime?
[in English] Really?
[in English] Why do you sound
different, Ms. Audrey?
[giggles]
[in English] Actually, I'm not Audrey.
[in English] But I am single
and available just for you!
Wait. Are you AFAM?
Because my nose is bleeding
from all this English.
I need subtitles.
[in English] Wait. Who is this?
[Jona on the phone] Okay.
He really speaks in English…
Well, fine. I'm ready to fight.
[in English] Um, my name
is Jose Bernardo Carandang!
[Jona on the phone, in English]
You can call me Jona!
[in English] I'm 22 years old,
from the place where religious
devotion meets affordable shopping!
Baclaran!
[in English] Hey, is this, uh…
0900-020001-00?
[in English] Correct!
[in English] I think
this is destiny, mister--
- [in English] Hello?
- [quirky blipping]
[in English] Hello?!
[in English] She gave you
a different number.
[in English] Yes, she did.
[in English] Maybe she's not
over her ex or something.
[in English] Just forget about her.
[suspicious music playing]
What's this?!
That was an AFAM. Now he's gone!
Who were you talking to, Jona?
Exactly. You've been speaking
English nonstop.
I almost ran out!
Almost!
Um, wrong number. Looking for…
Audrey?
- Audrey?
- True.
Isn't that the name
of Brother Atoy's girlfriend?
Yes.
You're late on the news!
They're not together anymore!
They broke up!
[Jona] Oh, really?
Is that confirmed, Siony?
I'm not sure.
But that's the rumor.
What a shame.
They looked good together.
Like me and Emerson.
- Oh. Gosh, girl.
- [Mona] You brought up Emerson again.
She had to connect it.
- She's really head over heels.
- [Jona] Mmm-mmm. Crazy.
[Mona] Oh, oh, oh.
[in English] We have information.
Ms. Lily Santiago, no longer in Manila.
[in English] We are still looking for her.
[in English] What about the man
who broke into the embassy?
[in English] Did you find him?
[in English] We shared his photo
with our security team.
[in English] The man is a total mystery.
[in English] It's harder to find him
without his name.
[in English] We might need
an expert tracker to find this guy.
Viktor.
[in English] I value our friendship.
[in English] I will never
steal anything from you!
[in English] If you want,
I can help you find this man.
[in English] I know
a very good tracker, a man hunter.
[suspicious music playing]
[line rings]
[in English] Hello, Ambassador.
[in English] We have a slight problem
with the man who broke into the embassy.
[in English] I think
we need Mr. Dmitri's help.
[in English] We need a tracker.
[tense music playing]
Karla, how's your application
to be an usher?
Here it is, brother. I already applied.
[in English] Usher intern.
- Hmm.
- [Emerson, in English] Very good.
As for me, I'll be a waiter.
I'll go in as a waiter,
so I can observe their movements.
What about the clothing for me
and Brother Kurt?
I'll handle that.
By tomorrow, everything will be ready.
Remember, our target is Boss KM.
Kevin Martinez.
And the suitcase with five million pesos.
[in English] Five million pesos.
We better rest now
so we can go full force tomorrow.
[Karla] I agree.
[Emerson] Wait.
[quirky warp]
What's this?
You'll wear that.
It's the uniform
of Atoy's new breakout group.
The Children of the Thread,
led by yours truly.
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Me.
This is all we'll wear?
Of course not!
We'll layer it.
But suspenders are required.
Go on, put them on!
- This is Emerson's baby!
- [Emerson] No…
Don't-- It won't be seen.
It's our brand identity!
We need to look solid
for our first mission.
[Karla] How do we attach this?
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
The Operation Suitcase.
[huffs]
[Karla] Let's try it.
Does this go at the back?
- [Karla] Feels like a backpack.
- [Ame] It's tight.
Oh.
Okay.
- Let's take a group selfie.
- Hmm?
Yes, send it to Atoy.
No, I'll take the picture.
I can't be seen.
- Join the next one.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- [Emerson] Next time.
- [Ame] Yes.
- [Emerson] Okay.
- There, 1.5, 2.5.
Hold it like this.
You hold it, Ame.
- Oh! Then I'll be the only one visible.
- Brother, come on.
Okay, okay. Fine, fine.
- [in English] Okay.
- Fix it!
- I'm not visible!
- Wait, I can't see Sis Ame.
- Hurry!
- Adjust, adjust. Adjust, correct!
0.5, right?
- [overlapping chatter]
- There, there! That's it.
[Emerson] We're all visible now.
[in English] Smile! One, two, three.
- [camera shutter snaps]
- [Karla, in English] Yes!
That's cute! Ohh!
Okay, okay, okay.
- [Ame] Oh, with you this time.
- [Emerson] Join in, join in.
- We won't send it to Atoy.
- [overlapping chatter]
- [in English] Okay.
- Wait, wait.
Let's check.
Everybody say, Children of the Thread.
[all] Children of the Thread!
- [camera shutter snaps] Child of Emerson!
- Oh, no.
- [giggles]
- [camera shutter snaps]
[music ends]
[phone blips]
SIS AME
[melancholic music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Sis Ame?
Did you see the picture I sent?
Yes, but…
why are you all wearing the same outfit?
We have a mission tomorrow.
Atoy isn't here.
He has another assignment,
so we'll handle it instead.
The Children of the Thread!
Children of the Thread?
Wait.
Why am I not included?
I'm the OG Child of the Thread of Tatoy.
Yes, of course.
You're the original Child of the Thread.
But Tatoy won't allow you
to join the mission.
It's better you stay safe with your mom.
Okay.
Why do you sound sad? How are you there?
How's Mama Olga?
I'm okay.
But I miss you.
I miss you too, Ibyang.
Mmm, promise. I'll call you tomorrow
when our mission succeeds.
I'll tell you everything.
Just behave there, okay?
[in English] Always, Sis Ame.
[sneaky music playing]
Oh?
I thought you threw that away.
You finished it instead.
Not yet.
I'm just finishing the handle.
Why did you still work on it?
It would be a waste.
You worked hard on it.
Besides, once I finish this,
it's like we both made it together!
Right?
[melancholic music playing]
Okay. [clears throat]
Thank you for doing that.
So, to make it even,
so I can make it up to you,
I'll cook our breakfast. Hmm?
- What do you want?
- Anything.
Hmm…
All right, instant noodles, then.
But Tatoy said breakfast
should be nutritious.
So…
I'll add an egg.
Okay?
[sentimental music playing]
[music fades]
[knocks on door]
Anyone home?
Hey, Audrey.
You're early!
Hi, Ame. Um…
Is Atoy here?
I want to talk to him.
He left. He has work.
You know how it is.
[melancholic music playing]
Ah.
Um…
I wanted to say goodbye
because…
Janine and I are leaving.
We're going to the US.
Hmm, vacation?
[in English] Maybe.
[in English] Maybe for good.
[sighs] Ah.
Just call or text him.
What about Ibyang?
Is she here?
I brought cookies for her.
I also want to say goodbye.
Ah.
Ibyang's not here anymore.
[in English] For good.
What?
Why?
Where is she?
Her real mother took her.
What?
Who is she?
[in English] Is she a good person?
[in English] Is Atoy okay with it?
Does he trust her?
Why did she only show up now?
[scoffs]
You know, you're asking
the same questions Atoy asked Olga.
Better open those cookies.
I'll make us coffee
because this will be a long talk.
Mmm-mmm.
This must be what Ibyang mentioned.
So, her name is Olga?
Hmm? Mm-mmm.
They taste good, right?
[music fades]
[phone ringing]
[in English] Good morning!
Wow, my favorite person
in the world called so early.
[in English] What's up, Director?
[in English] Hello, Olga.
Come to my set. I need extras.
Huh?
I have a gig now.
I can't.
[director on the phone] Ah, too bad, but…
- I have producer friends from the US here.
- [sneaky music playing]
They're looking for new talents.
Who knows, maybe this is
your chance to be famous!
Really?
You know I've dreamed of that for so long.
Why now? When I'm full-time at this job?
Okay, fine.
Should I give the chance to someone else?
Wait.
[sneaky music playing]
[frustrated grunt]
Um, where is it?
You're quick to give it away, Director.
[director on the phone]
At the mall! Near your house.
Come on. Move!
Okay. Fine, fine.
I'll go there. Okay?
[in English] Okay, Director.
See you. Bye-bye!
- [phone blips]
- Ibyang.
Take charge of what I'm cooking, okay?
It just needs seasoning. You know how.
Can I come with you?
Huh? No way!
Stay here!
[upbeat sneaky music playing]
[Olga exclaims excitedly]
Do you think what we're going
to do later will be hard?
Looks like it'll be easy.
- Really? Really? Okay.
- [man 1] We'll handle it.
Bye-bye.
[man] Let me just call the director.
Psst, psst. Friend!
Hey! Wait. What are you doing here?
Hmm? Why?
I thought your wallet was already thick.
Where's--
- Who?
- Where's-- Where's the little one?
She's not here. She's at home.
What? You left her? Alone?
- Sis, you prioritized taping.
- My God. What's this?
She can handle herself.
Don't worry too much.
Besides, I won't miss this.
I won't miss my chance to be famous.
- [Charmi] Wow.
- I love my craft, you know?
[in English] Craft.
Wow. What happened?
I thought this was all for money?
Of course, that too.
But… You know.
Do you see that?
- The one in the denim vest.
- [Charmi] Oh?
- [Olga] He'll see my talent.
- [inaudible]
He's going to be the solution,
so I can finally get out
of being a starlet!
[in English] I'm gonna be a star.
[in English] I'm gonna be a superstar!
[exclaiming]
- [phone ringing]
- Wait, someone's calling!
There.
Oh, Nora Aunor called from her grave.
She said don't steal her title!
- Overacting.
- [giggles]
I'll wash these later when I get home.
Maybe Mama's hungry.
Oh, here.
[whimsical music playing]
[director] Listen, listen!
Everyone, come here!
Yes! Hi, Director!
- [director] Where's my AD?
- Hello, Director!
Hey, stand behind me.
- [mutters]
- Okay, everyone.
Here's what will happen
in the scene later.
Armed men will massacre you!
You'll all be terrified!
- [gasps]
- [director] Show me fear!
- [director] And you'll be helpless.
Then they'll shoot you all.
[imitates gun firing sound]
Like that! Okay?
Are my instructions clear?
Yes. Thank you…
- Director! Director, is it okay
- [in English] Oh, yes, darling?
if I suggest something?
Because isn't it boring
if we all just agree to get shot?
Maybe one of us could fight back?
It can be just me.
Is that okay, Director? Because, you know…
To add some action.
- I like that.
- Right?
- Here's what I'll do, Director.
- [director] Mmm-mmm. Let's see.
- So, when two men approach, right,
- Yes.
- I'll jump.
- [director] Oh?
When I jump, they'll shoot.
I'll dodge, so it'll cramp.
The bullet will graze me.
But others here will get hit.
- [director] Who?
- Them, them.
- Ah, that works.
- Yes, they can.
- [director] Hey, take notes. Unbelievable.
- Then…
- [director] Yes, then?
- I'll punch like this.
- Oh, yes. Beautiful.
- Like that, okay.
Then I'll kick like this.
- [director] Riveting. Yes.
- Then they'll fall.
[goon actor 1] The job would've been easy,
but she's making it hard.
Exactly.
Olga's such a nuisance!
Feeling main character!
[goon actor 1] It doesn't matter.
She'll get killed anyway.
Later, I'll riddle her with bullets.
I'll use them all on her.
[both cackle]
- [goon actor 1] She's done for.
- [cackles]
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
[pensive music playing]
They're going to kill Mama?
[music swells, concludes]
Ah, is everything ready?
Okay. I want your fight scene
to look good.
- [in English] Yes, Director!
- I want it in one take!
- Straight through!
- [in English] One take, Director!
- Okay, Director!
- I'll check over there.
[director] Hey! Fix your shots!
- [director] Okay, let's rehearse!
- Direct-- Director, this is where it goes.
This is a gun, Director, a gun.
Okay. You at the back, react, talents.
- [director, in English] Rehearsing!
- Here, two guns.
- [in English] Okay.
- [in English] Five, four, three, two.
[in English] And action!
[in English] Action!
I'll do this, then this.
- [thumping and grunting]
- [screaming and panicking]
Then I'll block this.
Then I'll do this!
[grunts and groans]
I'll throw like this!
- [screaming]
- Run away now! Run!
That's it, Director! That's it!
Go, go! Run!
[in English] And cut it!
[pleasant music playing]
Ah, excuse me.
Have you seen my mother?
Children aren't allowed here.
Please help me.
They're going to kill my mother!
Go to the police.
No one's being killed here.
There is, believe me!
[gunshots in distance]
[sneaky music playing]
- [thumping and grunting]
- [screaming and panicking]
Run now! Run!
[screaming and panicking]
- What are you doing there?!
- [grunts]
Chase her!
[grunts] I'll kill you!
- [action music playing]
- [screaming and panicking]
[whimpering]
[foreboding music playing]
Mama!
[music swells]
[grunts]
[gasping]
- [man] What happened?
- [director, in English] I'm so sorry.
[in English] I-- I can explain!
[in English] Hey! Cut!
[director] What's happening here?!
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
I spoke to the child.
[Atoy on the phone]
Why didn't you tell her about your job?
And you left her alone at home.
Sorry!
Your setup is amazing.
- [in English] Co-parenting?
- Hey!
Could he be the father?
[Olga] That Ibyang…
She'll answer to me later,
when I get home.
[Janine] Because when…
I saw the shoes of Uncle Red's friend,
they were the same as the shoes
of the man who tried to take me before.
[Audrey] Tell me.
Do you know the man
who tried to take my child?
UP NEXT
[man, in English] Scammer!
[panting]
Mama?
- [grunts]
- Are you okay, my love?
[in English] We will proceed as planned.
[in English] But remember, the decoder
must be taken alive.
[Samir, in English] He might be here too.
[in English] Be careful.
This man has many faces
and can be very dangerous.
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix this ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias